The Lu Group is eyeing the Gu family's weakness
They won't make a move anytime soon
But Gu Chengze will look into you
He already has
He's still using the same old tricks
Worried
If he finds nothing
he'll find a way to label you
For the Fu family to verify identity
one of the key clues
is the old scar on the left wrist
What are you looking at
Your hand
Old scar
Got it when I was a kid
Can't remember much
If someone tells you one day
you could have had another identity
what would you do
What do you know
I just think
you shouldn't always be called a bodyguard
I don't care what others call me
It's enough that you know who I am
Are you going back
Did you know all along
The day you chose me you said three months
later they would beg me to look at them